Field, T. J. Collection of Retirement (Early Retirement) Study Data 5792
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
T. J. Field Collection of Retirement (Early Retirement) Study Data
1957-1963
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Field, T. J.
5792
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Study data about early retirement, collected by T.J. Field
5706172
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 07, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4016: Frederick Slavick Retirement Study Files 5059: U.S. Emergency Board No. 142 Records 5280: U.S. President's Commission on Pension Policy Papers 5293: New York State Teachers Association Records 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5685: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5736: Barbara Wertheimer Additional Files 5792: T. J. Field Collection of Retirement (Early Retirement) Study Data 6046: Archives Union File (AUF) 6047: Archives Information File 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files 6174/004: NYSUT Field Services Department Files 6174/005: NYSUT Legislative Department Files 6174/011: NYSUT Mid-Hudson Regional Office Files
Retirement.; Early retirement.; Field, T. J.
5706172
- Companies Refusing Intensive Study, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Early Retirement (Misc.), 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Atlantic Refining, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Early Ret., 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Early Retirement Charts - Originals (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Electric Storage Battery Company, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- General Mills, Incorporated, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Inland Steel, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- International Salt Company, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Int. Salt - Early Ret., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- McCory Corporation, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Oneida LTD., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Scott Paper, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Standard Oil Company (NJ) Early Retirement, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- S Ohio, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Current, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Retirement, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)